http://www.stantonandkilleenwines.com.au/policies/privacy-policy

HomeOur Wines
Shop All WinesSparkling WinesWhite WinesRed WinesNV FortifiedsBlending Fortifieds (Bulk)Vintage FortifiedsHome BarrelsSpecialsHome Barrels & Blending
About Home Barrels & Bulk FortifiedsBuy Bulk Fortifieds (Bulk)Buy Home BarrelsAbout Us
Our StoryOur TeamCareersNews at S&KVisit Us
Cellar DoorRegional Grazing PlattersVirtual Cellar DoorGroups & ExperiencesThe Quinta Club
About the Quinta ClubMember Club PacksContact Us
Contact UsCareersFrequently Asked Questions
Privacy policy
Stanton and Killeen Wines understand the importance of your information and are committed to protecting your privacy.
We have appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information we collect to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure. These procedures are consistent with The Privacy Act National Privacy Principles (amended December 2001)
When personal information about a person is established to be inaccurate, incomplete and not current Stanton and Killeen Wines will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and current.
No warranty is given that the information is free of infection by computer viruses or other contamination, nor that access to the website or any part of it will not suffer from interruption from time to time, without notice. All links to other websites included on this website are provided for convenience only and Stanton and Killeen Wines do not accept any responsibility for the accuracy, availability, or appropriateness to the user's purposes, of any information or services on any other website.
Data Security
Stanton and Killeen Wines will take reasonable steps to protect the personal information it holds from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.Information will be stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities.Stanton and Killeen Wines will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose to which the customer has consented.All Stanton and Killeen Wines staff wil be trained in their obligations under the Information Privay Act 2000Data containing personal information will not be held in any open or accessible location overnight.
Online purchases
We have implemented security measures designed to provide the peace of mind you should expect when purchasing goods over the internet. Your credit card details and other sensitive information is protected using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology. For addresses beginning with HTTPS, all information sent to this site is encrypted, protecting it from interception by unintended recipients.
To view details of our security certificate, please click on the Global Sign logo on the Check Out page.
All payments are processed via a 128bit SSL connection to eWay - Australia's leading payment gateway. For further security information on eW
